what's up everyone tv5 here with a very
special video today
now it's getting close to halloween and
[ __ ] so I decided to bring out like the
old ouija board
that I just had like sitting around like
in my attic for like all year because
you know it's
it's includes halloween people want to
hear like stories about ghosts and [ __ ]
and I have like this crazy ghost story
like
that that I don't think I’ve really told
my channel but
you know ben hurst like one objective of
the sock Underground
well it might sound crazy but I think
he's been haunting my ass for like a
really
really long time like for like the past
six or seven years and [ __ ]
like I have dreams about him like one
time like actually about like three
years ago I bought
out the ouija board but and
and like I like sat down and like he
like moved on his heart
on its own it's it's and it's feel like
his name like ben hurston [ __ ] like
ever since then I’ve just been too
scared to touch this thing
but I thought hey you know what with
halloween miles will take the chances
let's see if we can contact ben hurst
again although this time
on camera I don't know maybe he'll be
he'll beat you to try
some [ __ ] but I don't know we should try
so so all I know is that I have to like
you know like put all of my energy into
this thing
and maybe maybe i'll contact him
who knows like what that's the rule
right mama
yeah yeah yeah I just gotta put all my
energy into this [ __ ]
and if if we are lucky tonight
ben hurst the director of sock around
will contact me
van hurst are you here
ben hurst are you here I'm way
oh [ __ ]
b I i didn't even move that I mean
i mean [ __ ] what the [ __ ]
oh [ __ ] I I'm hardly putting any
pressure
into this e it's spilling his name again
this happened three years ago whoa oh
[ __ ]
ben hurst is that you is if
is that if that is you been us go to
eight
oh do you see how fast that [ __ ] was
what the [ __ ] what
a mama you seeing this I think venus is
here
ben hurst is this you
oh oh [ __ ] he said yes
oh [ __ ] bennett how long have you been
haunting me
he went straight he went straight to
seven
i I told you I he's been hiding my
smelly ass for six to seven years I i
don't know I don't give a [ __ ]
ben hurst why are you here
ben hurst like are you angry with me
no so you're not even jealous
you're not even just that I i pretty
much starts like i
made a man
you said no but you hesitated are you
jealous
are you just be honest with oh he's
going straight
yes oh [ __ ] ben hurst what's going on
uh are you that jealous be awesome ben
has like
do you think I’ve at least been doing
good
with soccer do you think I’ve at least
been doing better than you
g you gay [ __ ] oh
oh oh d oh good
you're smelling good so you think I’ve
been doing good talking around
good goodbye you what the [ __ ]
what the [ __ ] what is this
bed hugs what the [ __ ] what are you
doing
ben huh stop bring it back
what are you doing what are you doing
what oh [ __ ] what the [ __ ]
yo ben huss what the [ __ ] you gotta stop
that
oh [ __ ] that was ben huss
that was that was him he tried to steal
my [ __ ] [ __ ]
he tried to take it takes like on back
to hell you got to take it to hell with
him
like you can't make that [ __ ]